Question:
If you have a look at your colorful plot, it's clear that people live longer in countries with a higher GDP per capita. 
No high income countries have really short life expectancy, and no low income countries have very long life expectancy. 
Still, there is a huge difference in life expectancy between countries on the same income level.
Most people live in middle income countries where difference in lifespan is huge between countries; 
depending on how income is distributed and how it is used.

What can you say about the plot?
 A. The countries in blue, corresponding to Africa, have both low life expectancy and a low GDP per capita.
 B. There is a negative correlation between GDP per capita and life expectancy.
 C. China has both a lower GDP per capita and low expectancy compared to India.

Answer : A

